-[rapid beeping]
-Run!
-Run. run. run! Go. go!
-[Dale] I got an H2S leak
at 5272. Send Hazmat and EMS.
We're partners barely a month.
Look how well we're doing.
Oh. no. you're not partners
with me.
You're partners
with a 22-year-old kid.
You bet on him to fail.
so he would owe you.
and so I'd owe you.
I don't owe you
a fucking thing
and neither does he.
Hey. every time you
take a fucking breath.
-you owe me. Thomas.
-Really?
Every time you take
a fucking breath!
[Cami] I now know why Monty
was so stressed.
The company has no money.
You might want to hang here
for a minute. okay?
Well. now. why would I do that?
Because I'm-a get
a little rough.
-[grunts]
-Come here.
Who's the gangster now?
It's like I'm looking
into a mirror.
You ever bar tend before?
Just for fun.
You ain't gonna think
it's fun here.
It could get interesting.
Who died?
My mother.
[T.L.]
It's a disease. you know?
And it killed a part
of her I loved.
and left us with
the woman you knew.
Funeral's Friday.
♪ I got a little change
in my pocket ♪
♪ Going "jing-a-ling-ling" ♪
♪ Want to call you
on the telephone. baby ♪
♪ I give you a ring ♪
♪ But each time we talk ♪
♪ I get the same old thing ♪
♪ Always.
"No huggee. no kissee ♪
♪ Until I get a wedding ring" ♪
♪ My honey. my baby. don't put
my love upon no shelf ♪
♪ She said.
"Don't hand me no lines ♪
♪ And keep your hands
to yourself" ♪
♪ Ooh. baby. baby. baby ♪
♪ Why you gonna treat me
this way? ♪
♪ You know I'm still
your lover boy ♪
♪ I still feel the same way ♪
♪ That's when
she told me a story ♪
♪ About free milk and a cow ♪
♪ And said.
"No huggee. no kissee ♪
♪ Until I get a wedding vow" ♪
♪ My honey. my baby ♪
♪ Don't put my love
upon no shelf ♪
♪ She said.
"Don't hand me no lines ♪
♪ And keep your hands
to yourself" ♪
♪♪♪
Shit!
♪ Go. man. go! ♪
♪♪♪
♪ gentle music ♪
♪ slow. somber music ♪
[lighter flicking]
-Come out here for a smoke?
-[laughs softly]
The opposite.
Needed some fresh air.
Yeah.
How'd you finish out the night?
Uh...
Haven't counted yet.
Don't count it out here.
[chuckles]
Count it in the office.
I need to tip the bar backs?
Twenty percent.
So. what are you thinking. huh?
-We gonna see you tomorrow?
-[scoffs]
-It is tomorrow.
-[chuckles]
Are we gonna see you today?
I'm a single mother.
I can't be getting home
at 5:00 in the morning
to a baby who wakes at 7:00.
Yeah.
You know. I'd count that stack
before you say no.
Two nights a week here is like
two weeks of nights
anywhere else.
Two nights a week I could do.
I assume Friday and Saturday
are the best days?
When oil's booming...
[chuckles]
...it don't make no difference.
[exhales sharply]
Every night's Friday night.
♪ Slow. gentle music ♪
♪♪♪
Cooper.
What are you doing?
[grunts]
Uh...
Came to get my coat?
It's too hot for a coat.
A dress coat. Or a sports coat.
Why didn't you just get it?
You have a key.
Well. you told me to leave.
Didn't feel right going in your
house without your permission.
But it felt right to sleep
on my porch like a stalker?
I called you
and you didn't answer.
so I got worried.
Come on in.
[keys jingle]
[lock clicking]
[keys clatter]
Are my things still in the...
Still in the closet. Cooper.
[fridge door closes]
[water running]
[inhales sharply]
-[sighs]
-[water turns off]
Uh. so. you're working
at the Patch?
Mm-hmm.
Supposed to be
a pretty rough place.
Lives up to its reputation.
What's with the coat?
Big meeting?
Uh. Grandmother died.
Oh. Cooper. I'm so sorry.
It's okay. I-I didn't know her.
She had a troubled life.
but still a funeral
all the same.
-In town?
-In the Panhandle.
Canadian.
Is that far?
It's a drive.
Give me five minutes to change.
You don't have to do that.
It's fine.
You were there for me.
I'll be there for you.
Like I said.
I didn't know her to miss her.
You don't want me to go?
I want you everywhere.
Then give me five minutes.
♪ Slow. dramatic music ♪
[water running]
♪♪♪
[sniffles]
I thought you didn't
know her to miss her.
It's not her I'm missing.
[laughs softly]
Didn't miss me enough to fight
for me. though. did you?
You told me to leave and I left.
That's exactly what I meant.
If you didn't want me to leave.
then why did you tell me to go?
Because the only option
you were offering
was me completely
uprooting my life.
Leaving my home. my family.
everything I've ever known
because you made some money.
Hasn't occurred to you
to come up
with another option. has it?
So you left.
You left.
♪ Slow. somber music ♪
How far is the drive
to Canadian?
Seven hours.
Wake me in five.
[door opens]
♪♪♪
Y'all got court?
We're going with you.
Well. hell.
y'all don't even know her.
-We ain't going for her. amigo.
-Well. I appreciate it.
but I don't even know
why I'm going myself.
to tell you the truth.
[Angela]
Don't you boys look nice?
Look at you. Dale.
Told you a little fruit
and yogurt
-would melt that fat away.
-[Dale] Yes. ma'am.
You been working out. too?
Uh. no. ma'am.
I've been taking Adderall.
With these 20-hour days.
this coffee
-just ain't fucking cutting it.
-[Tommy] Who knew
the health benefits
of amphetamines?
It's not amphetamine.
-That's all it is.
-[Angela] Well.
it's working.
-so good for you.
-[Dale] Thank you.
-Hey. baby. Y'all ready to go?
-Morning.
-Let's go.
-You. uh.
you want to ride with me?
We'll all fit in the Expedition.
Oh. good. Five of us
in the same car for seven hours.
That's gonna be fun.
Well. it could be
if you let it. Daddy.
Sweetheart.
we're driving up through
the Panhandle of Texas
to a funeral.
That makes it
impossible to be fun.
Only with that attitude.
Tommy. you want me to drive?
I am very focused right now.
[door opens]
[Rebecca]
Wait. what happened?
[Walt]
We're still piecing it together.
One of your drivers
ran into a pickup
parked on the easement
to your well.
What. wait. who was parked
on our easement?
Not sure. Ain't got him out yet.
There's a chance
he was already dead
when your man hit him.
which is a good thing for you.
I would imagine.
Your driver. however...
did not survive.
-and that's not good.
-[sighs]
No. I would say it's not.
Great.
I got to go.
I'll call you when I land.
Hi.
-You mind?
-[Charlie] Oh. Yeah. well...
Wouldn't matter much if I did.
It's not my-my plane.
Here. have a seat.
[clears throat]
It's pretty windy. so if
you want a drink. get it now.
Once we're in the air.
we're gonna need everyone
to remain seated
with their seat belts on.
-Came prepared.
-Uh. define "pretty windy."
Gusts up to 70.
Great.
Nervous flyer?
I have control issues
that can manifest
in certain circumstances.
Flying is one of them.
♪ "Wolf Song"
by Andrew Lockington playing ♪
♪ Long. long ride
on another day ♪
♪ Come alive on another day ♪
♪ Know that I don't run
a little. know why? ♪
♪♪♪
[exhales]
[sighs]
Oh. Monty.
I am trying very hard
not to be mad at you.
Focusing on the futility of it.
My therapist thinks
I should write you a letter.
Who knows? Maybe I will.
Brought you a few things.
[sniffles]
Uh...
[chuckles]
Your favorite.
Harder to get
than I would have imagined.
You didn't mention
they're illegal.
[sniffles]
And...
[chuckles]
You can have this again.
but they have a rule that. uh.
you can't leave the bottle.
So you're gonna have
to drink it all now.
[sniffles]
[exhales]
I found this in your closet.
Thank you.
Oh. Monty. the 30th anniversary.
♪ Slow. somber music ♪
I thought we'd have 20 more.
♪♪♪
-[airplane rattling]
-What the hell is that?
It's called
a TRT standing takeoff.
It's because of the headwind.
They do it a lot
on shorter runways.
You. uh. you're probably
gonna feel a bit of a jolt.
[high-pitched whirring]
[shrieks]
What the fuck? Oh. my God!
Oh. my God!
[gasping]
Oh. my God.
[shrieking]
I'm sorry!
Please. God.
Hey. hey. hey. hey.
Look at me. look at me.
This is not how we die.
All right?
-Okay.
-Now I need you to grab my knee
and squeeze
the hell out of that.
-All right?
-Your hand is fine.
No. no. no.
I need you to grab my knee
because I'm pretty sure
you've broken my hand.
-Oh. I'm sorry.
-All right. there you go.
-[shrieking]
-Hey...
It's okay.
-There we go.
-[sighs]
-[laughs]
-[panting]
[panting. sighs]
Everybody okay back here?
Yeah? Okay?
Okay. should be smooth
until our descent.
Until our descent?
So. how about that drink?
-Please.
-Great.
There.
Hmm. What is this?
That is vodka
and watermelon juice.
-It's pretty good. right?
-Yeah. this is dangerous.
Mm. I add simple syrup.
Hmm. Because vodka
and fruit juice alone
doesn't create
a bad enough hangover?
A hangover?
I work in the oil fields. miss.
We sweat out
the hangover by noon.
[Rebecca sighs]
You think the turbulence
will be the same when we land?
It's the same wind
blowing through Midland.
I'm sorry to say.
just blowing harder.
♪ "Hard Luck & Circumstances"
by Charley Crockett playing ♪
-Mm.
-Oh. very good.
That's the spirit.
♪ When it comes to bad luck ♪
♪ I got perfect timing ♪
♪ All the stars just align ♪
♪ Me and trouble ♪
♪ We're old friends ♪
♪ We understand
each other fine ♪
[cutting out]
♪ Because it's hard ♪
The music stopped.
Ain't no cell service
out here. honey.
-What about the regular radio?
-It's right here.
-[static crackling]
-See that?
[sighs]
People wonder why I left.
No. they don't wonder
why you left. honey.
-They wonder why you came back.
-Well. not to worry.
I have plenty of road trip
playlists.
What are y'all
in the mood for. huh?
-Ooh.
-Okay. I've got yacht rock.
sexy salsa.
You know. it's like. um...
-♪ Havana. oh. na-na. mm. mm ♪
-[fingers snapping]
♪ Half of my heart
is in Havana. oh. na-na ♪
-"Oh. na-na."
-How do you know that song?
[Angela]
That's what it is.
[sighs]
Geez.
Look at you
sad Sallys in the back.
Honey. we're driving
to a fucking funeral.
I know where we're going.
It doesn't mean that the drive
can't be pleasant.
It can't be pleasant!
We're driving
to a fucking funeral!
If you're not careful.
they're gonna be burying
someone else
at that son of a bitch.
you talk to me like that.
[exhales]
Okay.
Yacht rock it is.
[stifled laugh]
Oh. do you find something funny?
It is the antithesis
of humor. Angela.
I don't know
how to explain what it is.
Well. why don't you try. Neil?
-Nate.
-I know what
your fucking name is. okay?
And after
you've explained yourself.
maybe I'll use it.
Maybe I'll choose
another fucking name for you.
I don't think you should
explain what it is. Nate.
It's a trap. Neil.
I'm waiting.
Yacht rock
would be my preference.
[Angela] Well. it's your lucky
fucking day. Neil.
♪ Oh. the canvas
can do miracles... ♪
What? I mean.
I'm driving you to smoke?
No. you're driving me
to suck Freon
out of the back of an AC unit.
-I'm settling for a cigarette.
-Fine.
We'll all just be miserable
for the whole fucking day.
[sighs]
♪ Sailing ♪
♪ Takes me away ♪
♪ To where I've always ♪
♪ Heard it could be ♪
♪ gentle. pensive music
[train horn blowing]
♪♪♪
[Cooper]
Hi. Uh. Mr. Norris?
Thanks.
Hey. Grandpa.
Cooper.
That ain't your sister.
No. sir.
I'm Ariana.
Thomas.
I'm so sorry
for your loss. Thomas.
Oh. honey. I lost her years ago.
Today. I'm just saying goodbye.
Sit down.
You're prettier
than he deserves.
[chuckles softly]
He doesn't have me.
-No?
-Mm-mm.
Mm. You're in the habit
of taking six-hour drives
to funerals for people
you don't know
with men you don't like?
This is a first.
[soft laughter]
Smarter than you deserve. too.
You don't even know what game
you're playing. do you?
If you'd clue me in.
I'd sure appreciate it.
Got to ask her.
Play your cards right.
she might even
tell you the rules.
Of course.
she's gonna change them.
At least you'll know
what they used to be.
[laughs softly]
This ain't your first rodeo
with one of these. is it?
This is my fifth rodeo.
If we're keeping count.
Time comes there's
been too many to count.
-That's where I am.
-[door opens]
What are they putting
in your water?
Hi. TL.
You don't age.
Mm...
I'm so sorry. baby.
Ainsley?
Hi. Grandpa.
Last time I saw you.
you were that big.
Now it's like
a sunflower come to life.
Who are these fucking clowns?
[clears throat]
Uh. Dale. sir.
That weren't a question
I expect you to answer.
They work with me. Pop.
Here for emotional support.
I expect.
Yeah. something like that.
As if you loved her enough
to need it.
As if there's anything to love.
Let's not get all misty
and forget
who we're burying. all right?
Let's get this over with.
♪ Slow. somber music ♪
♪♪♪
[pastor]
From Psalm 34:18.
"The Lord is near
to the brokenhearted
and to the crushed in spirit."
Dottie's life was troubled.
but she has at last found peace.
I'd like to offer her husband
an opportunity
to offer a few words.
Mr. Norris. is there anything
you'd like to say?
Not to you.
It's not to me. it's to God.
God already knows it.
The Lord is my shepherd.
I shall not want.
He maketh me
to lie in green pastures.
He leadeth me to sit
beside still waters.
He leadeth me...
...in the paths of righteousness
in His name.
♪ Gentle. atmospheric music ♪
[dishes clattering softly]
[waitress]
Chicken-fried steaks.
I have two chicken
Caesar salads.
no dressing. no cheese
-and no croutons.
-It's me.
You don't say.
Right here with the other.
You realize that's just
lettuce and chicken?
-I do.
-Cancer?
Vanity.
I'll pray for you.
-Thank you.
-Homemade corn dogs?
Here. Thank you.
You got two corn dogs
for lunch. Pop?
Best thing on the menu.
-Thank you.
-[waitress] You're welcome.
[T.L.]
Mmm.
T.L.. how do you like your home?
[chuckles]
It's not my home.
It's an old Motel 6
they converted into a place
where we wait to die.
Fire took my home.
Your house burned?
Whole Panhandle burned.
Well. from what?
Same thing that always burns it.
Drought. 70-mile-an-hour winds.
fucking power line
on a pumpjack.
Yeah. they need to bury them.
You know how much that'd cost?
You know how much
that fire cost?
How many generations
of ranchers was wiped out?
Oh. I'm not defending it. Pop.
I'm just saying
that's why they don't do it.
[T.L.]
Money is the reason.
[Tommy]
It's always the reason.
How come nobody's
talking about her?
I've been to a few of these.
You lay them to rest.
say goodbye.
have a feast and...
...talk about them.
Remember what they meant to you?
She was your mother. right?
I don't have any memories
worth sharing.
[clears throat]
All right. here's one.
since you're so curious.
Tommy.
I remember
coming home from school...
...and finding her naked.
face down in the bathtub.
I was 14 years old.
Dad. he was working on
the offshore rigs in Louisiana.
I pulled her out by the hair...
...and I called the ambulance.
and they walked me through CPR
till she puked water in my face
while I was blowing air
in her lungs.
And she sat up...
...and she looked at me
like I was a stranger.
And then she pulled
her leg back...
...and she kicked my nose
through the back of my head.
Then she got up
and walked into the kitchen
and made herself
another fucking drink.
I went and put everything
I owned into a backpack.
'cause a backpack's all it took.
Never been back
in this town since...
...till a week ago.
There was no miracle
involving my mother
other than her managing
to die of old age.
And he was too weak
to leave her.
So I left all of them.
I didn't come here to
mourn her passing. honey. I...
I came here to celebrate it.
[sighs]
I'll be in the car.
Here you go. Pop.
Sort through that.
That ought to take care of it.
[clears throat]
[door opens]
I can tell you why...
[door closes]
What killed her soul.
But it don't really matter now.
I guess.
When she was 17.
I ain't never seen
someone more alive.
I remember driving past
this park in Amarillo.
all these sports fields.
Kids playing soccer
on one and...
football on another.
And on one field.
all the sprinklers were running.
It was August
and hotter than hell.
And all those sprinklers
made a rainbow above them.
She shouts. "Stop the car!"
[chuckles]
And she leaps out
and races through
those sprinklers...
...chasing a rainbow
and dancing beneath it.
Soaked from head to toe.
It was the most beguiling thing
I'd ever seen.
Someone that free.
But...
...demons run faster
than rainbows.
and hers caught up to her.
I spent 60 years
waiting for her rainbow
to return.
It never did.
But that's life.
And I wasted mine on hope.
♪ Somber. atmospheric music ♪
♪♪♪
Go say goodbye to him.
I said goodbye to him
years ago. honey.
You need to hear
the story he just told us.
Oh. the one about
dancing with rainbows?
I've heard the story. babe.
[sighs]
Let's go. Come on.
♪♪♪
Thank you.
Good luck. man. Take care.
♪♪♪
[Tommy]
Hey. Cooper?
-We still got to talk. bud.
-I'll call you tomorrow.
No. don't call. Come by.
-Love you. Mom.
-Love you.
-[car doors opening. closing]
-Bye.
What?
I think I understand you
better now.
Well. if you don't mind
explaining me to me.
-I'm all ears.
-Oh. I plan to.
-[car doors opening. closing]
-[engines starting]
♪♪♪
[train whistling]
♪ "Time Bomb"
by Whiskey Myers playing ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
-[whooping]
-♪ My head's pounding ♪
♪ As the kick drum's drowning ♪
♪ Everything I got left ♪
♪ To say... ♪
Okay. don't-don't...
don't waste it.
-[laughs]
-Shit.
-Hold it straight.
-Oh. yeah.
Hold it straight.
Shit! Fucking hell.
What the fuck was that?
This is absolutely
fucking terrifying.
-[shrieking]
-♪ As above. so below ♪
-♪ Praying for another ♪
-Oh!
♪ Day ♪
♪ Like a time bomb ♪
[laughs]
Whoo!
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ gentle. atmospheric music ♪
[sighs]
Car's waiting outside.
I'm gonna list the house.
-This house?
-Yep.
Call Martha Williams
at Williams-True
and ask her to come out.
♪♪♪
[Tony]
Evening. Mrs. Miller.
-Welcome back.
-How are you. Tony?
Good. Please. this way.
Okay.
I have y'all
in the corner over here.
[Cami]
Okay.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[soft laughter]
Grabó su nombre.
Ha scritto suo nome.
-Sí.
-Ah! Hello.
Oh.
-Hello. new best friend.
-How are you?
I'm good.
-Very well.
Hello. Cami. How are you?
Good to see you.
I hope you don't mind
my wife joining. Here.
She gets very jealous
when I'm dining alone
-with beautiful women.
-Please. I wish
I had joined my husband on a few
more of his business dinners.
More than you know.
-Thank you.
-I took the liberty
of ordering you a tequila.
Ooh. wow. Good memory.
My wife has the memory. I just
have the good sense to ask her.
[Bella] Do you want me to sit at
the bar and let you talk shop?
I don't know. how big of a shop
are we talking?
It's big.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
All right.
We'll solve the world's problems
before the first course.
I promise.
-Okay. Ciao. bello.
-Ciao. Bella.
Let me grab the drink.
I'm all ears.
Your company invests
in drilling expeditions?
We finance exploration. yes.
-And do you have a ceiling?
-Well. everybody has a ceiling.
but we have yet to find ours.
Well. I need to drill
an existing well.
It's an offshore rig that
was damaged in the hurricane.
In the gulf?
Correct. But there's no risk.
It's an existing gas field.
and the location's
been thoroughly mapped.
The challenge isn't
in finding the gas.
it's getting to it.
And the challenge with that
is the time it takes.
What's the timeline?
If we start drilling in 90 days.
we should reach the field
in about ten months.
-And what's the loan amount?
-I'd say
$325 to $350 million.
Isn't this something that Tommy
should be negotiating?
Well. it's my company.
I'll be paying the note.
I should be negotiating it.
Your husband. he left you
quite a mess. didn't he?
It wasn't intentional.
But yes. he did.
Snakes are cannibals.
Did you know that?
I did not.
They eat rabbits.
mice. squirrels. quail.
But they also eat each other.
I know my business is similar.
But the snakes. we have a code.
We only eat other snakes.
No rabbits. no mice. no quail.
I'd like to help you.
but I can't negotiate with you.
Not because you're a woman.
You're not a snake.
Have Tommy reach out.
Are you calling Tommy a snake?
Well. maybe not a snake.
but. uh.
he's a hawk.
And hawks?
They eat snakes. too.
[dish clatters softly]
Thank you.
Don't you worry about a thing.
The answer is yes.
I'll let the snakes
figure out the rest.
You drank your drink already?
-Uh. maybe.
-[Cami laughs]
[laughter]
It's gonna be a long night.
♪ Slow. atmospheric music ♪
[Ariana] Don't know
how you turned out so kind.
[Cooper]
I don't know about "kind."
I try to do what's right.
what's decent.
Don't always do it. but I try.
[laughs softly]
Like I said. kind.
Would you like to come inside?
-You okay with that?
-[chuckles]
I didn't ask you
to jump in my bed.
I asked if you would like
to come inside.
I would like that.
[Ariana laughs softly]
[engine turns off]
[door closes]
My house.
I know.
It's not much. but it's mine.
And I like it.
Miguel's abuelita's house.
Down the street. his tíos. tías.
Sus primos.
They're all right here.
Having met your family.
I can understand
why being close to them
is not a priority of yours.
But it's everything to me.
And I will work.
You might not like the job.
but it doesn't matter
'cause you're
not the one doing it.
And next time I kick you out.
you don't just leave
and stay gone.
You figure out why I did it.
fix it...
...and then come home
and tell me how sorry you are.
I'm sorry I...
struck oil and got rich.
-I-I won't let it happen again.
-[laughs]
-You're on real thin ice. flaco.
-I know.
Um...
I am sorry.
I didn't ask
for your dreams or...
which ones
I should make come true
and which ones
should just stay dreams.
You can't make
my dreams come true.
Only I can do that.
Got it?
Got it.
Okay.
♪ Soft. hopeful music ♪
This is very confusing.
[laughs softly]
I know.
It's confusing to me. too.
I want to buy you
a new dishwasher.
[both laugh]
-Okay. fine.
-No. really.
Can we at least take
a trip or something?
Trip where?
I don't know.
Where do you want to go?
Hmm. You might
just figure this out.
It's pretty simple.
All I got to do is
ask you everything.
Hmm. My God.
he did figure it out.
Okay. now you can jump
in my bed.
[laughs]
♪♪♪
♪ soft. somber music ♪
Patient suffered traumatic
transhumeral amputation.
A.E. right side. BP 98/54.
-HR 122.
-Car wreck?
Rig. Caught his arm
beneath the hydraulic shaft.
Put him in three. Let's go.
He's awake.
[indistinct chatter]
[doctor] ...certain amount
of tissue damage to the area.
And that's going to have
some other complications
further down the line.
So. what he's currently
dealing with
is severe ocular inflammation
and severe
pulmonary inflammation.
Now. what we don't know
at this point
is whether this damage
is permanent.
His breathing is improved.
Once the ocular inflammation
is down.
we'll look at what
neurological damage may persist.
When you. when you say
"neurological." you're...
Memory issues. cognitive issues.
People can lose sense
of taste and smell.
How is his nervous system
affected?
Does he have full motor skills?
Is there numbness
in his extremities?
Only time can answer
these questions.
-But he is talking.
-He can speak.
He can respond when spoken to.
Does he have family close?
They're all in Houston.
He's gonna need his family.
Can we see him?
Uh. he just
regained consciousness.
so let's keep it brief.
Hey. how's it going. my man?
-Boss?
-What's up?
[King] You scared the shit
out of us. bro.
Yeah. we thought you was dead.
[laughs softly]
You ain't the only one.
How you feeling. man?
My fucking eyes. man.
[BR] Yeah. you're one
lucky son of a bitch.
There's dead people and animals
all around that pumpjack.
-Yeah. We're all lucky.
-Yeah.
[nurse]
Okay. Jerrell?
Just gonna change your compress.
-All right.
-Get a nice cool one
-on there. Okay?
-Yeah.
Head up. There we go.
How come I can't see?
You took it off. right?
Just keep your eyes closed. hon.
But-but... Hey.
How come I can't see?
-It's all right.
-I'll send in the doctor.
-Hey. Boss. Boss. Boss.
-Hey. Yeah. I'm-I'm right here.
-I'm here. I'm right here. man.
-I can't fucking see.
Your eyes.
they're inflamed. okay?
They're puffy and they have...
have fluid coming out.
Th-That's why you can't see.
that's what the doctor said.
so...
Did-did he say I'm-a see again?
♪ Slow. somber music ♪
I ain't no doctor.
but I-I'll go get him.
[Jerrell]
Wait. Boss.
How the fuck's a man supposed
to take care of his family
if he can't see?
You know how many mouths
I got to feed.
Yeah. I do. I do.
Let me go get the doctor.
-Doctor! Doctor!
-Jerrell.
-I'm-a go get him.
-Man. doctor!
-Man. relax.
-Doctor! Doctor!
Doctor! Doctor!
[woman over P.A.]
Rapid response. ICU 11.
Rapid response.
♪♪♪
[soft crying]
Hey. baby. what's wrong?
[sniffles]
You save her life.
and then
she kicks you in the face.
Who does that to their child?
I don't care
how many rainbows she chased.
I hope God takes
one of those rainbows
and just shoves it
right up her ass.
Honey. my mother
was far away
from gods and rainbows.
That ain't where she went.
honey. if you know what I mean.
[softly]
Yeah.
But I'm gonna tell you something
that might help explain it.
I had a sister.
And. uh...
...she died from SIDS
at four months old.
What is that?
It's when a baby dies
in his sleep
and they don't know why.
It. uh. maybe it rolled
on its stomach or.
you know. the little lungs
couldn't get enough air.
you know.
-[exhales]
-Nobody knows. honey.
[sniffles]
But. uh...
Well. the loss broke her.
and. uh. it just
snapped her in two.
I think she was just so scared
to feel any kind of love again
after that that...
that she drugged and drank
her soul to death.
That's not an excuse.
Well. sweetie.
I didn't say I could justify it.
I-I just said I'll explain it.
that's all.
What. you think
she was hard on me?
My poor father. he...
he was scared to death of her.
He would spend a whole year
at a camp...
...and not come home once.
Just send the checks.
He wasted his life
hiding from her.
That's so tragic.
Yeah.
But it's my tragedy. honey.
not yours.
-Okay?
-Okay.
♪ Slow. somber music ♪
I have to say. there's not
many people on this planet
that care enough
to cry over something
that somebody else went through.
You got a big old heart
beating under that hood. baby.
[whispers]
I got it from you.
-Love you.
-Love you. baby.
♪♪♪
I've lived through some
heart-wrenching fucking days
in my life. Tommy. but this one?
[sighs]
Here we go.
I swear. Tommy.
Like. of all the calamities
that I have endured...
Now. what calamity
are we talking about now?
The great sunscreen shortage
of 2007?
How about our marriage?
[chuckles]
We solved that. didn't we?
I mean. I don't see
a ring on my finger.
I do. Are we not calling
those little shiny things
that reflect on the ceiling
"rings" anymore?
This is from our first marriage.
All right? It doesn't count.
It's tainted.
Well. give it back to me.
I'll trade the son of a bitch in
and buy a new truck.
[scoffs]
Shit.
You know. there are
so many things about our lives
that need to be fixed.
and do you know where it starts?
[quietly]
This ought to be good.
No. where does it start. honey?
Where it always starts.
The beginning.
I'm not following you.
Your father.
He's rotting away
in some miserable excuse
for a nursing home with nobody.
Nobody loves him.
That was his choice.
You can't be a father
to our children
if you can't be a son to him.
Okay. two things: first of all.
stop watching those
fucking daytime talk shows.
And second of all.
our kids are grown.
Job done. They're adults.
Tommy. my life
is with old folks.
Okay? And no matter who
they were when they were young.
now that they're old. I mean.
every regret. every mistake...
...they have chewed them up
and mulled them over.
and they are sorry.
I mean. they're deeply.
deeply sorry.
I mean. he deserves peace.
And you're the only one
who can give that to him.
How am I gonna do that?
Um...
Why did you close the door?
So you don't wake
the whole house when I tell you.
♪ Slow. atmospheric music ♪
[Tommy] Are you out
of your fucking mind?
[radio DJ 1]
Good morning. Permian Basin.
If you've got a swimming pool.
today is the day to get in it.
[radio DJ 2] I'd fill it
with ice cubes first.
[radio DJ 1]
102. the expected high today.
[radio DJ 2]
Summer came early.
and when summer comes
to West Texas.
-it stays.
-Till November.
[radio DJ 2] So. if you've
got things to do outside.
-you better get to them.
-Stop wasting time.
-[DJ 2] Stop it right now.
-That's the theme
of the day.
and here's a song to go with it.
from The Red Clay Strays.
["Wasting Time"
by The Red Clay Strays playing]
[song playing over radio]
♪ Another year around the sun.
and nothing's been done ♪
♪ I got to get out
of this state I'm in ♪
♪ My wheels have been spinning.
but I ain't been moving ♪
♪ Got to get back
on the track again ♪
♪ I've been stuck in a rut ♪
♪ Just a-kicking up mud ♪
♪ And I'm sick of waiting
round for the change ♪
♪ I got my foot on the gas.
gonna make things happen ♪
♪ And do them all my own way ♪
♪ Can't wait. won't waste ♪
♪ Ain't wasting time
no more... ♪
-[sighs]
-[toilet flushes]
Oh. God.
-Hi.
-Morning.
Okay.
You need a ride to your car?
No. uh. I'll just...
call an Uber once
I've gathered up my dignity.
[chuckles]
Oh. come on.
Don't do that. Don't regret it.
I had a lot of fun.
-I'm sure you did.
-[laughs softly]
You're gonna pretend
like you don't remember?
-No.
-No?
No. it's all coming back to me.
[chuckles]
Mind if I use your shower?
What's mine is yours. love.
Thank you.
[sniffles]
You do know I saw it all
last night. right?
Yeah. well. it was dark
last night. so...
Looks pretty good
in the day. too.
I'm so glad you think so.
[exhales]
-[knocking on door]
-Yes?
[Charlie] Hey. it's me.
Remember. from the bedroom?
-Hi.
Oh. towels.
You need fresh towels.
Right in the cabinet over there.
the far right cabinet.
-Great. Thanks.
-Cool.
Okay. What?
Look. it's too early
and I'm too hungover
for you to be charming.
Okay. fine. I'll just. uh.
I'll call you later
and be charming then.
-Great.
-Cool.
You know.
there's a body oil in there
that is. uh. pretty good.
you should try it out.
-Thank you.
-Oh. you know.
and the aromatherapy discs
are pretty good.
You just throw them on the drain
-and you like...
-I got it from here.
It's not my first shower.
Oh. it's not? Okay.
Well. I'm-I'm in a rush.
I've got to run.
-Okay.
-Yeah. I'll call you later.
-Can't wait.
-Good.
[water running]
[sighs]
Okay.
Aroma therapy pod. nice touch.
♪ Soft. atmospheric music ♪
♪♪♪
What are you doing here?
Ignoring my better judgment.
'Cause that's what
pleasing my wife requires.
You're here to please your wife?
Yeah. I am.
And what would it take
to do that?
Having you in our lives again...
...getting to know
your grandkids
and getting to know her.
I'm pretty used up. son.
Yeah. so am I. Pop.
So. what's the plan?
You move me to a home closer
and just forget about me there?
No. actually. we're thinking
about bringing you home.
Listen. Pop. I'm not
gonna try too hard at this.
If you want to stay out here
and die. fine.
Or you can come with me
and watch the sun
all damn day long.
You can watch it set
and sit out there all night.
Second chances
don't come around that often.
And this one ain't ever
coming around again
for neither one of us.
It's about to go.
♪♪♪
Let me go grab my things.
I already got them.
You ain't ever setting another
foot in that fucking place.
I'm not sure I deserve this.
What does deserve
have to do with it. Pop?
♪♪♪
♪ gentle music ♪